dear customer I am an ICICI Bank
representative and I'm going to take you
through an incredibly easy journey of
video kyc for your personal loan so
let's begin log in with the link which
you have received for video kyc on both
SMS and email before you open the link
please ensure that you are in a strong
Network area or have a good Wi-Fi
connectivity on your device also follow
a few instructions for smooth process
keep original pan card a blank paper and
a black pen for Signature along with you
while doing the video
kyc look into the camera while verifying
the
details while capturing the photo make
sure you're in a proper attire with
white background proper lighting and
keep your eyes
open do not show AAR card or share your
Adar number during the
call also no third person should be be
visible or audible during the call now
once you have opened the link you will
get an OTP through a SMS and an email to
log to the video kyc portal after
entering the OTP please click on login
then you will see a video kyc option
click on the same to initiate the video
kyc call after this you will see a popup
with video kyc instructions click on
okay the next screen will show you your
name and your pan number you will need
to enter your Adar number and accept the
terms and conditions then click on
verify now only once and wait for the
Adar OTP to be received on your Adar
linked mobile number please avoid
multiple clicks and ensure that the
mobile number linked to Adar is active
as you will receive an OTP triggered by
uidai on it enter the OTP and click on
continue then your Adar photo and
address will will be fetched from uidai
please confirm that your address details
and current address as per the
application form are correct by ticking
after confirmation you need to click on
initiate video kyc button only once and
wait for the web page to load please
avoid multiple
clicks after initiation the system will
connect you to an agent request you to
wait till you connect to the agent when
you are connected to the agent you will
see a chat window and the agent will
initiate a two-way video call please
accept it when the video call starts the
agent will ask you to share your
location and other verification
parameters please note that you need to
be in India while initiating video
kyc the agent will guide you through the
rest of the process and that is your
video kyc Journey yes it's as simple as
that with ICICI Bank